adakoo.com 2014-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Adakoo

This Privacy Policy covers adakoo.com is treatment of personally identifiable information that adakoo.com collects when you are on the adakoo.com site, and when you use adakoo.com’s services. This policy also covers adakoo.com’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that adakoo.com’s business partner’s share with adakoo.com.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that adakoo.com does not own or control, or to people that adakoo.com does not employ or manage.

adakoo Network Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on the adakoo.com site. 

adakoo.com collects personally identifiable information when during registration, adakoo.com asks for your name and email address. Once you have sent us this information and sign in to our services you are not anonymous to us anymore. 

adakoo.com uses information collected for two purposes:

(a) Information provided to us is used to customize the advertising and content you see and to inform you about special offers, new products and other services which are offered completely free of cost. adakoo.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. Unless it is specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than adakoo.com, you will be notified prior to the data collection or transfer.

(b) adakoo.com may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when:

we have your consent to share the information

we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested and given your consent

we have to cooperate with the investigations for unlawful activities

Members can edit their adakoo User Account Information and adakoo profile by sending an email Member’s adakoo account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in not being able to access any members-only area of the iIoveIndia network But the residual information will remain in our archive records. adakoo.com can change this policy any time.

Our members are our assets and we will never knowingly do anything to harm this trust. Any information given voluntarily to us by you is used to enhance your experience on our site, to provide you with interactive or personalized elements on the sites and to better prepare for future content based on your areas of interests. We gather this information to determine which areas are liked by our site members and which are not liked based on the traffic to those areas.

We do not track what individual members read, but rather try to determine how well each page performs. This helps us continue to provide better services to you. We also use the information that is gathered to tailor the content to best suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our members.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google is use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
